ACTWU's Textile Division Records 5619/038
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Administrator Local 415T Jack Coury (Norristown, Pa.), 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Administratorship Michael Merola Local 416T T. Ankosas Dyeing & Processing Co. Mount Holly, N.J., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Administratorship: Local 465T Richard A. MacFadyen, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Administratorship Local 482T Painesville, Ohio Harold Bock, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- ACTWU- Administratorships Local 933T Glenville, CT., 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Administratorship Local 1020T York, Pa. Robert Hinkle, Administrator, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Local 1340 Garold Rulon Administrator St. Louis, Mo. Ex. Council Mtg., 1975-1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Administratorship - Local 1553 (Marionette Mills, Coatesville, Pa.), 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Local 1599 Frank Cuccio Administrator Bridgeton, N.J., 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Administratorship Local 1618T Blue Ridge Winkler, Middletown Del. Carl Frazier, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Local 1665 Allentown, Pa. Administrator: E. Sherman Hearing Officer: M. Moreno, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Appt. of Administrator Local 1669 Hazleton, Pa. Edward Sherman, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Local 1669 Hazleton, Pa. Administrator, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Administratorship, Local 1705 Rochester, N.Y. Joseph W. Lipowski, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Local 1707 Montgomery, Pa. Carl Frazier, Administrator, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Local 1707 Montgomery, Pa. Adm. Bruce Dunton Appointed, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Local 1728 Rocky Mount, N.C. Julius Fry, Administrator, 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Local 1765, Nitro West Virginia Harold Bock, Administrator, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Administratorship Local 1771 Chicago Joint Board Pat Cronin, Administrator (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Administratorship Local 1771 Chicago Joint Board Pat Cronin, Administrator (2 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Local 1817, Allentown, Pa. Administratorship, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Local 1848 Hazleton, Pa. Administratorship Jack Coury, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Administratorship Local 1859 Robert Manini, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Local 1868 Hazleton, Pa. Administratorship, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Administratorship Local 1888 Saegertown, Pa. Bert Demers Administrator, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Local 2028 Paducah, Kentucky Administrator Marion Groce Appointed, 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Administratorship Local 2300 Lebanon, Pa., 1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)